911勤务中心 你有什么麻烦？
911, what is your emergency?
我刚射中了我哥哥
I just shot my brother.
帮帮我
Help me!
那女孩正在治疗
The girl is now recovering from a shooting
在南郊区受到的枪击
on the far South Side.
突发新闻 两名青少年
Breaking news, two teens,
致命枪击的受害者…
the victims of deadly gunfire...
2016年底的芝加哥
Chicago will end 2016
凶杀案大幅上升…
with a surging murder rate as city leaders...
这里是"摇摆早晨"Shade 45频道
It's Sway in the Morning. Shade 45.
我们要谈谈在芝加哥发生的事
We gotta talk about what's happening in Chicago.
你已经接通了
You got... ...on the line right now, man.
你知道问题出在哪里吗
You wanna know what the problem is?
问题在于他们不关心我们
The problem is they don't care about us.
问题在于我们的教育程度不够
The problem is we don't got enough education.
17岁的男孩被枪击…
Seventeen-year-old boy who was shot and killed...
一位12岁的女孩
A 12-year-old girl
正在治疗
recovering from gunshot wounds
昨晚枪击案中的枪伤
suffered in the shooting last night.
762起凶杀 3500多起枪击案
762 murders, more than 3,500 shootings.
没希望了
There's no hope, guys.
政府不会去帮你的
The government ain't coming for ya.
比以往任何时候都严重
Things are worse than ever before. So sit there...
我们要继续这一话题
We gonna keep this topic goin'
因为芝加哥必须做些什么
because something has to give in Chicago.
B-9116警车 紧急情况 枪击紧急情况
Squad B-9116, emergency. 10-1 emergency.
警察受到枪击 一位警员受伤
Shots fired at the police. We have an officer down.
我正从南环区前往 我们在伟基河畔路上
I'm coming in from South Loop. We're on Wacker Avenue.
正前往芝加哥北医院
We're heading toward Chicago North.
大约两分钟后到
ETA about two minutes.
他胸口多处枪伤 情况紧急
Multiple GSWs in his chest. He's in critical condition.
让个外科医生在急诊室门口等着
Have a trauma surgeon meet us at the ER entrance.
请注意一位警员正前往
Be advised. Officer en route.
多处枪伤
Multiple gunshot wounds.
大约两分钟后到
ETA, two minutes.
我们能行的 保持清醒
We can do it! Stay awake!
让开 该死的
Move! Jesus Christ!
快
Come on!
快 我们走
Come on, buddy, let's go.
快
Go!
什么情况
What do we have?
胸部枪伤 大出血
Gunshot wounds to the chest. Massive bleeding.
腾出创伤诊室
Clear the Trauma Room!
加油 坚持住
Come on, stay with me, buddy, all right?
别闭上眼
Don't close your eyes.
- 别闭上眼 - 让开
- Don't close your eyes. - Out of the way!
- 没有脉搏 没有脉搏 - 该死的
- No pulse! No pulse! - Jesus Christ!
快来帮我
Somebody help me!
加油 朋友 坚持住
Come on, buddy. Stay with me, buddy! Come on!
你们过来 护士
You two. Over here. Nurse.
是 医生 我这就过去
Roger that, doc. I'll be right there.
叫科尔西医生来 马上叫科尔西医生来
Get Dr. Kersey. Get Dr. Kersey now!
蓝队去急诊室
Blue team to ICU, please.
Blue team to ICU.
…固定和扩张
...fixed and dilated.
科尔西医生一号创伤诊室需要你
Dr. Kersey, you're needed in Trauma One.
- 克利斯 接替我 - 好的
- Chris, switch with me. - Got it.
谢谢
Thanks.
多处枪伤 脖子上也有一处
Gunshot wounds, including one to the neck.
- 防弹衣？ - 是的
- Vest? - Yep.
- 医生 拜托了 - 等等
- Doc, please. - Hold on.
开胸托盘 五袋0型血 马上
Thoracotomy tray now. Five units of O-neg, stat.
再有五袋送往急诊室
And five more en route to the ER.
准备好手术室
Get the OR ready.
是 医生
Yes, doctor.
宣告不治
Let's call it.
死亡时间0点24分
Time of death, 12:24 a.m.
6分钟到了这里
Got here in six minutes.
没法开得更快了
I couldn't go any faster.
这不是你的错
It had nothing to do with you.
他的心跳停止了 失血过多
His heart stopped. He's lost too much blood.
我们已经尽力了
We did everything we could.
我深表同情
Sorry for your loss.
凶嫌在二号手术室 医生
Shooter's in Two, doc.
对不起
Sorry.
科尔西医生 二号手术室 科尔西医生 二号手术室
Dr. Kersey, OR Two. Dr. Kersey, OR Two.
怎么 现在你要去救那个杀了他的禽兽？
What? Now you're gonna go save the animal that shot him?
如果可以不必的话
If I can.
猛龙怪客
这表好像跑得慢了
I think it's running a little slow.
也许该换个新的了
Maybe it's time for a new one.
不 我喜欢这个
- No, I like this one. - Mmm.
他们说是9点
They said 9:00.
她会被录取的
She's going to get in.
我知道 我只是怀念信件通知
I know. I just miss envelopes.
而不是网络上这些玩意
None of this online crap.
天啊 太好了
Oh, my God! Yes!
听起来像是有好事
That sounds like a good scream.
听起来像是有大好事
That sounded like a very good scream.
嗨 你们好
Oh, hey, guys, what's up?
嗨 孩子 你想吃早餐吗
Hi, baby. You want some breakfast?
你好吗
- Mmm-hmm. - How are you? How you doing?
- 我很好 - 是吗 你饿吗
- I'm good. - Yeah? You're hungry?
- 是的 我很饿 - 想吃鸡蛋吗
- Yeah, I'm starving. - Want some eggs?
好的 麻烦了
Mmm. Yes, please.
你期待你的比赛吗
Are you excited for your game?
只是场球赛而已
Eh. It's just a game.
喂 我刚才好像听到楼上有动静
Hey, I thought I heard a noise upstairs.
你听到什么了吗
Did you hear anything?
是啊 我好像也听到了 是怎么回事
Yeah, I thought I heard something, what was that?
谢谢 我被录取了 我被录取了
Thank you. I got in. I got in! I got in!
真高兴 孩子
So happy, honey.
我真为你高兴
I'm so happy for you!
我要住在纽约了
I'm gonna be living in New York City!
我周末会飞回家洗衣服 好吗
I will fly home on weekends to do laundry, okay?
我保证
I promise.
好 好 好的
Okay, okay, good.
天啊 我问问苏菲有没有被录取
Oh, my God. I have to text Sophie to see if she got in.
我们的女儿要上大学了
Our girl is going to college.
我很高兴
I'm happy.
- 真的 - 是吗
- Really. - Yeah?
但你的脸上看不出高兴
- Mmm-hmm. - I think you have to tell that to your face.
亲爱的
- Mmm. Baby. - Mmm.
别停 过来
Don't stop! Come here!
- 注意防守队员 - 快 快
- Watch the defender. - Go, go, go!
加油 乔丹 加油 乔丹
All right, come on, Jordan. Let's go, Jordan!
- 乔丹 - 加油
- Jordan! - Let's go!
我老是以为
I guess I always had it in my head
她会去西北大学 离家近点的
that she'd go to Northwestern. Someplace close.
是啊 那时我想读德州的大学
Yeah. You think my dad was happy
你以为当年我爸也很高兴吗
when I wanted to leave Texas to go to college?
这不一样
Well, this is different.
怎么不一样
How's it different?
只不过现在我们家长是该放手了
It's just that now we are the ones that have to let go.
这是犯规 喂 这脚抬太高了
That's a foul! Hey! That was cleats up!
裁判是死人吗
- What the fuck, ref? - Oh.
没必要吧
Really?
我只是没想到发生的过么快
I guess I didn't think it would happen so fast.
这个传球太糗了 布里安娜 你自己也知道
That's a bullshit pass, Brianna. You know that!
我觉得我们会经常见到她
I think we're gonna see her more than we think.
因为我们有感恩节
Because we've got, um, Thanksgiving,
我们有圣诞节
- we've got Christmas... - Mmm.
我们还可以去纽约
And we get to go to New York City.
犯规 这是又一个犯规
Foul! That's another foul!
- 真是的 - 别激动 朋友
- Jesus Christ! - Take it easy, pal.
会心脏病发的
You're gonna give yourself a heart attack.
我没跟你说话  住海边啊
I wasn't talking to you, Lake Shore Drive.
不 事实上 你在跟所有人说话
No, as a matter of fact, you were talking to everyone.
用词注意点 这里有孩子呢
Just dial down the language, there's kids here.
我要是不呢
Or what?
保罗 拜托
Uh, Paul, come on.
我如果是你的话 我就闭嘴了
I would just shut the fuck up if I were you.
这是好主意 你为何不这样呢
That's a good idea. Why don't you do that?
就当是我 闭上嘴
Be me, and just shut the... Fuck up.
你觉得很幽默吗
You think that's funny?
再说一遍
Say it again.
来啊 幽默男
Come on, funny guy.
再说一遍
Say it again.
现在说不出话了吧
Now you're quiet, huh?
- 说啊 说啊 - 住手
- Come on! Come on! - Stop it!
- 住手 住手 - 过来
- Stop it! Stop it! - Come here.
对 让你老婆来保护你
Oh, that's right. Get your wife to defend you.
娘炮
Pussy.
没事的 没事
It's all right. All right.
然后那人就走到我爸面前
Okay, so then the guy gets right in Dad's face, okay?
开始推换他
And he starts shoving him
让比赛都停下来了
and it literally stops the game.
喷了我一脸口水
Spitting right in my face.
还得逼着我出面
I had to get in the middle of it.
我都想揍他一拳
I was gonna punch the guy. Right?
你为何不揍他一顿呢
Why didn't you whoop this guy's butt?
就像你当年那样
Like in the old days.
幸好你妈拉着我
Thank God your mom came over.
等等 爸爸 你当年？
Wait, Dad, the "old days"?
是啊 你爸当年爱打架
Yeah, your dad was a scrapper.
是啊 我爱打架
Yeah, I was a scrapper.
是嘛 你以没跟我说过
Really? You never told me that!
要是在当年就动手了
He would've, back in the day.
告诉她 告诉她
Tell her. Tell her.
我以前常跟我爸打架
- I used to fight my dad. - Oh.
整天打
Fighting all the time.
他大喊大叫 在家里哭
You know, he was screaming and crying in the house.
你猜是谁哭
And guess who was crying?
是我 我每次都打输
Me. I lost every fight.
- 真不行 - 我还是爱你的 爸爸
- Terrible. - I still love you, Dad.
你该学以色列武术 学好了
You should take Krav Maga. You study that.
等你到了大学 当有的男生
This way, when you go to college, and these guys,
对你不客气的时候
when they get a little too aggressive with you,
你就知道该做什么
you know what to do.
别以为我在开玩笑
Don't look at me like I don't know what I'm talking about.
不 我只是说 我已经知道了
No, no. Yeah, I'm just saying, like, maybe I already know it.
喂 喂
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- 乔丹 - 好了 好了
- Jordan! - All right, all right.
我被控制住了
I tapped out.
是真的 她每周一
Seriously, she trains Monday,
周三 周五都训练 你得小心她
Wednesday, and Friday, this one. Watch out.
- 真的吗 - 我在训练
- Really? - I'm training.
我还在Tribeca看到一家拳击馆
And I actually found a boxing gym in Tribeca
很多女模都去那里
that all the supermodels go to.
所以我以后要去那里
So I'm gonna start going there.
说到大学 你的博士学位到手了吗
And speaking of college, how about your PhD?
你真有心 还记得这事
Oh, that's very nice of you to remember.
怎么样
How about that?
经过15年的努力 我很快就成为医生了
Yes, 15 years in the making, I am soon to be a doctor.
- 为妈妈干杯 - 多好啊 来
- Cheers to Mom, right? - How about that? Come on.
两个科尔西医生 你能相信吗
Two Dr. Kerseys. Can you believe it?
两个医生
Two doctors.
- 你要叫我医生吗 - 是的
- Are you gonna call me Doctor? - Yes, I am.
- 是吗 - 我要叫你老婆医生
- You are? - I'm gonna call you Dr. Baby.
- 为科尔西医生干杯 - 谢谢
- Cheers to Dr. Kersey. - Thank you.
另外两个不是医生的科尔西呢
How about two Kerseys that aren't doctors?
- 我俩也干一杯 - 不是医生的科尔西
- How about cheers to us? - Non-doctors.
我想买蓬松的羽绒服 UGG拖鞋
I wanna get the big puffy jackets, UGG slippers...
多少钱
How much?
两千
Two grand.
怎了 两千怎了
What? Two grand, what? Hey, man.
我犯了点错
You know, I've been convicted of a crime.
倒不是说我是坏人
I mean, it's not like I'm a criminal, but...
这件羊毛外套？
This cashmere?
没问题
It's okay.
谢谢了
All right, thanks, man.
保罗 谢谢你
Pauly, thank you.
不客气
No worries.
钱在他那里 不是我
He's got the money. Not me.
非常感谢
Hey, thank you so much.
MJ…
MJ.
公牛队球迷？
Bulls fan?
不 这是我的名字
No, it's my name.
- 米格尔·哈维尔 - 喔
- Miguel Javier. - Ah.
是啊 可是啊
I know, I know, I know!
拉巴马饭店  我记住了
La Bamba, at 1:00. I got it.
再见
Love you!
- 是拉万达饭店 - 而且是8点
- It's La Fonda. - At 8:00, okay?
3点钟 我记住了
Three o'clock. I got it.
周三8点 拉万达饭店
Wednesday, 8:00, La Fonda.
好 那样的饭店我不会忘记的
All right, I wouldn't forget a restaurant like that.
- 再见 - 再见
- See you guys. - Bye.
哇 你真漂亮啊
Wow, you look nice.
你也一样
So do you.
喜欢你的礼物吗
Do you like your present?
喜欢
Yes.
我也爱你
- Aw. - And I love you.
Aw.
是谁打来电话了
Oh, and who is this calling?
我不在
Oh, no.
嗨 苏珊 是的 他在
Hi, Susan. Yes, he's right here.
你们准备好了吗
You guys ready?
嗨 苏珊
Hi, Susan.
我正在试穿我的生日礼物
I was just trying on my birthday present.
不 我跟特里安排好了
No, I had worked it out with Terry.
他…
He's...
好
Okay.
好 回头见
Mmm-hmm. Yeah, see you soon.
特里发高烧了
Terry has a 104 fever.
那么没有在拉万达饭店的生日晚宴了？
So, no birthday dinner at La Fonda?
Mmm-mmm.
我去告诉法兰克叔叔
I'll go tell Uncle Frank.
- 对不起 爸爸 - 没关系 孩子
- Sorry, Daddy. - Oh, it's all right, hon.
我只惦记那个三奶蛋糕
I just had my heart set on that tres leches cake.
是啊 我也想吃 很快就能吃到的
I know, me, too. We'll have it soon.
好的 孩子
All right, baby.
我们明晚再庆祝
We will celebrate tomorrow night.
别担心 我保证
Don't worry at all, I promise.
尽量别睡着了
Try and stay awake.
好 我会的
Okay, I will.
- 好了 - 我会的 再见 老公
- Okay. I'm sorry. - I will. Bye, honey.
没事的
It's all right.
嗨 保罗
Hey, Paul.
生日快乐 老头
Happy birthday, old man.
拜托
Oh, come on.
- 第一排的票 - 你啥都没给我买
- First baseline. - You don't get me anything.
你们可要带我去看过比赛
You better be taking me to that game.
为什么不让拉万达饭店送餐呢 那样简单多了
Why can't we just Postmates La Fonda? It's so much easier.
我们的蛋糕要比他们的好得多
Our cake is gonna be so much better
因为我们是用爱做出来的
because we're gonna make it with love.
但拉万达也是用爱做的
Yeah, but La Fonda makes it with love.
我们也知道爸爸爱吃他们的蛋糕
And we know that Dad already loves it,
所以算是双赢
so it's kind of a win-win.
不 这是他的生日
No, it's his birthday.
他会欣慰我们出了力
He's gonna love knowing that we actually made the effort.
我们用心了
We did the work.
我们可以把厨房弄得一团糟
So we can make the effort to dirty up the kitchen,
然后当他回家的时候
and then when he gets home,
我们就假装做了一整夜的蛋糕
we just pretend that we cooked all night.
孩子 我们要做蛋糕
Honey, we're making the cake.
孩子 你能把我的iPad拿来吗
Honey, could you get me my iPad?
好像是在楼上的床头柜上
I think it's upstairs on the nightstand.
好的
Sure.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗨 苏菲
Hi, Soph.
我听不见你
I can't hear you.
我已经缩小到两个选择
Okay, so I've narrowed it down to two options.
要嘛是三居北路 要嘛是七号路
I'm thinking either Third North or Seventh Street.
三号北路那间房子卧室大
Third North has bigger bedrooms
但七号路那间房子的所在区域
but I think that Seventh Street is just, like,
感觉要好得多
a way cooler area.
孩子 你拿到iPad了吗
Honey, did you get that iPad?
是的 在你的床头柜里面 不是在上面
Yeah, it was in your dresser, not on it.
乔丹 你能下来吗 我需要它
Jordan? Can you please come down here? I need it.
乔丹 你马上下来
Jordan, come down here, right now.
妈 我在拿充电器 你急哈
Mom, I am grabbing a charger, relax.
你们今晚要做什么
So what are you guys gonna do tonight?
乔丹
Jordan!
天啊 你能放松点吗 我说了我这就下去
Oh, my God. Will you calm down? I said I'm coming.
快点
Now!
我要挂电话了
I'm gonna have to call you back.
我妈发神经了
My mom is being a total psycho.
不
No!
妈妈
Mom.
马上放下手机
Put the fucking phone down right now.
不
No.
求你们别伤害她
Please. Please don't hurt her.
别伤害她
Don't hurt her, please!
嘘
Shh.
嘘 唬
Shh. Shh.
接下来会这样
Now here's, uh, here's what's gonna happen.
你节省我们20分钟时间
Mom, you're gonna save me 20 minutes
去打开保险柜
by opening the safe.
好
Okay.
然后我要把你和你女儿绑在一起
Then I'm gonna tie you up with your daughter,
这样我们走远之前 你就没法打电话
so you won't be calling anyone till we're long gone.
好
Okay.
如果你这么做的话 就不会有人受到伤害
Now if you could do that, nobody gets hurt.
好
Okay.
听见了吗
- You understand me? - Mmm-hmm.
去吧
Go on.
妈妈 妈妈
Mom, Mom!
别伤害她 别伤害她
Don't hurt her. Do not hurt her.
这完全取决于你
Oh, that's entirely up to you.
没事的 妈妈 就这么做吧 去吧
It's okay, Mom. Just do it. Just go.
把她绑起来
Tie her up.
别胡闹
No fucking games.
我们要走了
We need to move.
喂
Hey.
喂 别胡闹 你是聋子吗
Hey, no fucking games. What, are you deaf?
把那东西拿开
Put that thing away.
好 放松
All right, man. Relax.
真是的
Jesus.
看住她
Just fucking watch her.
我老公有两只手表 还有现金
My husband has two watches, there's cash...
你们可以都拿走 随便拿
You can take it all. Whatever you want.
好的 谢谢你
That's nice. Thank you.
绳子在哪里 小妞
Where's the rope, girl?
去车库找找看
Check the garage.
别跟我玩健忘症
Don't get amnesia on me.
对不起 我只是不习惯
I'm sorry. I'm just not used to doing it
在枪口下开保险柜
with a gun pointed at me.
那就习惯一下
Yeah, well, get used to it.
你喜欢体育运动？
You play sports?
看你像是运动员的身材
You look like you play sports.
不
No.
嘘 - 不 住手
- Shh. - No, no, stop.
你说什么了吗
Did you say something?
请不要
Please don't.
你能行的
Oh, you can do it.
然后就完事了
And then we're done.
天 你很强壮
Goddamn, you're strong.
这很好
That's good.
不
No.
- 别 - 拜托你
- No, no, no. - Please.
没事的 这很好
It's nice. It's nice. It's good.
打开了
I got it.
喂 你急什么
Hey. Hey, what the fuck is your rush, bro?
我们没时间胡闹
We don't have time for this shit.
给我两分钟 拜托
Just give me two fucking minutes, please.
我拜托你 两分钟
I'm begging you, two minutes, please.
这不是那种派对 好吗
It's not that kind of a party, all right?
你别这么胆小好吗
Why don't you just stop being such a fucking pussy?
你干什么 你干什么
What the fuck? What the fuck, man?
该死的
God damn it!
操
Fuck!
该死的
Fuck! God damn it!
- 你这混蛋 - 不
- You motherfucker! - No!
- 不 不 - 你干什么
- No! No! - The fuck are you doing?
她划了我的脸
She cut my fucking face!
她能看到你的脸
She can see your fucking face!
妈妈
Mom!
乔丹 快跑
Jordan, run!
不管了
Fuck it.
外伤 两个人一级
Trauma, two incoming, Level One.
女性 17岁 颅底骨折
Female, 17, basal skull fracture.
女性 43岁 胸部枪伤
Female, 43, gunshot wound to the chest.
西蒙医生 你能帮我收尾吗
Dr. Simone, would you mind closing, please?
是 医生
Yes, doctor.
上心跳监控器
Put her on the monitor.
两次输血 给她输氧
Get two IV's and put her on oxygen.
是
Yes.
乔丹 睁开眼睛 睁开眼睛 乔丹
Jordan, open your eyes. Open your eyes, Jordan.
她需要输液
She needs to be intubated.
准备100毫升的异丙酚
Prepare 100 milligrams of propofol...
医生 等等
Doc, hold up, man.
没事的 没事的
It's fine, it's fine.
听着 保罗 出了些事
Listen. Paul, something's happened.
你不能进去
You can't go in there.
她们在哪里
Where are they?
保罗 保罗
Paul. Paul.
她在哪里
Where is she?
他们带你女儿去手术室了 医生
They took your daughter up to surgery, doc.
你老婆在二号手术室
Your wife's in Two.
露西
Lucy!
保罗
Paul...
我们已经尽力了
We did everything we could.
老婆
Baby.
我们的护照 乔丹的出生证
Our passports, Jordan's birth certificate,
2000美元现金
$2,000 in cash...
我的史丹佛大学毕业戒指
My Stanford class ring,
桌子上的两只沛纳海手表
two Panerai watches on the desk.
你能描述一下手表的样子吗
Can you describe the watches?
一个是纯黑的
One was all black.
另一个
The other one...
是个生日礼物 银色的和黑色的
It was a birthday present. Silver and black.
家里有什么枪械吗
Were there any firearms in the house?
没有
No.
很多这种人
A lot of these guys,
闯进住宅寻找枪 因为容易出手
they break in looking for guns 'cause they're easy to sell.
曾有两个混蛋溜进我家
I had a couple of assholes break in
寻找我的枪
to my house looking for mine.
你们觉得就是这样？
So that's what you think this was?
是抢劫过程发生意外？
It was a robbery gone bad?
最近在北岸地区发生了
Well, there have been a string of break-ins
一系列室内抢劫案
along the North Shore.
所以有这个可能
So we're looking at the possibility.
你说一系列 一系列是多少
You said string. How many in this string?
呃 在这9个月中有6起
Uh, six, in the last nine months.
6起？6起抢劫案 你都知道吗
Six? Six robberies. Did you know about this?
不 我不知道
No, I didn't know about it.
你们觉得这不重要
What, you don't think it's important enough
不需要告诉居民吗
to tell the residents?
每个嫌犯我们都张贴在社区巡守处
We post every crime on the Neighborhood Watch.
如果足够重大
If it's big enough,
媒体会选择报导
the media picks it up and reports about it.
否则就只是一般抢劫案
If not, these are just burglaries.
只是一般抢劫案
Just burglaries.
法兰克 这不是他的意思
Frank, that's not what he meant.
我只是想知道
No, I'm just wondering,
现在是否能足够引起他们的重视
if it's important enough now, to go on their radar...
你这是帮倒忙
You're not helping.
今晚很不幸
You guys, it's been a long night.
我们也了解了不少讯息了
I think we got enough to start with.
- 是的 - 是的
- Yeah. - Yeah.
这是我的名片
This is my card.
谢谢
Thanks.
上面有我的手机号码
It's got my cell phone number on there,
如果你知道别的情况的话
if you've got anything else.
谢谢你 雷恩斯侦探
Thank you, Detective Raines.
我理解你的愤怒
You know, I... I get that you're upset.
我们也火大了
We're upset, too.
但我们会抓住他们的
But we're gonna get these guys.
我再次向你致以哀悼
Again, I'm... I'm deeply sorry for your loss.
- 谢谢 - 谢谢你们抽出时间
- Thank you. - Thanks for your time.
科尔西医生 你女儿手术结束了
Dr. Kersey, your daughter's out of surgery.
她的手术很顺利
Her surgery went well.
她依然在昏迷中 但她情况稳定
She's still in a coma, but she's stable.
他们清除了血块
They were able to evacuate the hematoma
取出了弹片
and remove the bullet fragments.
我只知道这些了
I wish I had more to tell you.
我今天要带妈妈回家去找外公
So, I gotta take Mom home to Grandpa today.
法兰克叔叔会暂时接替我为你读书
Uncle Frank's gonna take over reading duties for now.
我非常爱你 非常爱 孩子
I love you so much. Oh, so much, baby.
我们很快再见 孩子
I'll see you soon, kiddo.
当露西的母亲去世时
When Lucy's mother passed,
她转身对我说：
she turned to me and said,
上帝为何这么早带走她
"Why did God take her so soon?"
我只能说：孩子 我不知道
All I could say was, "Honey, I don't know.
我想上帝自有其安排
I think it's part of His plan.
我们必须相信他的安排
And we have to trust His plan."
我们以前常来这里看她
We used to come up here and visit her and...
现在
Well...
我又来了
Now here I am.
我要说些我不该说的话
And I'm seeing something I was never meant to see.
怎么可能是上帝的安排
How is this part of His plan?
哪有这样的安排啊
How is this part of any plan?
谢谢你 保罗 谢谢你带她回家
Thank you, Paul, for bringing her home.
这是她想来的地方 和她妈妈葬在一起
This is where she wanted to be. With her mom.
我总有一天会去见她们
One day, I'll join 'em.
这里永远都有你的位置
There'll always be a place here for you.
谢谢
Thanks.
警方有线索了吗
Have the police gotten anywhere?
邻居看到有三个修理工 开着一辆白色面包车
One of the neighbors saw three repairmen in a white van.
警方似乎相当确定
The police seem pretty confident.
该死 快跑
Oh, damn. Run!
盗猎者 来
Poachers! Come on!
快走
Go, go!
人们依赖警察保护他们的安全
People rely on the police to keep them safe.
这就是问题所在
That's the problem.
警察只在
The police only arrive
案发后才到
after the crime has taken place.
这就像
That's like...
在狐狸
Trapping the fox
出了鸡窝才去捉鸡
as he's comin' out of the hen house.
如果一个人真想保护自己的东西
If a man really wants to protect what's his...
他就必须自己去做
He has to do it for himself.
这里是乐谱电台 我是曼考
All right, this is The Loop. I'm the Mancow.
7点15分 7点1刻
7:15, a quarter past 7:00.
早安
Good morning.
死亡之城又一个美好的周末
Another great weekend here, the city of death.
这个周末有48个人受到枪击
Forty-eight people shot over the weekend.
48个人中枪
Forty-eight freaking people shot.
13人死亡 情况越来越严重
Thirteen dead. And, uh, this... It's getting worse.
数字还在上升
The numbers are up.
不知道我们还能忍受多久
You wonder how much more of this we can take.
对不起 科尔西医生 还没一点线索
I'm sorry, Dr. Kersey, nothing yet.
一点都没有？
Nothing?
别急 这并不罕见
Don't be alarmed. It's not uncommon.
验尸一般需要一两星期
Forensics usually takes a week or two.
线人举报也是一样
Uh, same with informants.
喂
Hey!
对不起 有个混蛋要为我擦车窗
I'm sorry. Some asshole's trying to clean my windshield.
喂 够了 走开吧
Hey, that's enough. Go on.
撞死他就是了 不算犯罪
Run 'em over. Doesn't count as a crime.
我能这么做？
I can do that?
我的办公室里还有人
Look, I have someone in my office right now,
但杰克森侦探和我正在全力调查
but Detective Jackson and I are all over this, okay?
喂 够了
Hey! That's it!
有情况的话我们会通知你
We'll get back to you as soon as we have more information.
- 拜托 做点什么 - 是啊
- Come on! Just do something. - Yep.
- 你去死 - 好 我去死
- Fuck you! - Yes, fuck me.
给点零钱吧 拜托
Spare some change, man? Come on, man.
规范经济学和经济学的艺术
"Normative economics and the art of economics,
但却不能独立于
on the other hand, cannot be independent
实证经济学
of positive economics.
任何政策结论…
Any policy conclusion..."
苏菲
Sophie.
- 嗨 - 科尔西医生 嗨
- Hi. - Dr. Kersey, hi.
护士允许我进来的
The nurses let me come in here.
不 没关系
No, it's okay.
你来我很高兴
I'm glad you're here.
你还好吗
How are you doing?
我很好 你呢
I'm okay. How are you?
我还好 谢谢
Doing okay. Thank you.
你在念什么
What are you reading?
米尔顿·弗里德曼的"实证经济学论文集"
Um, Essays in Positive Economics by Milton Friedman.
这恐怕不能帮她醒来
I'm not sure that's gonna help her wake up.
是啊 很枯燥
Yeah, I know, it's boring.
呃
Um...
但这本书在纽约大学的暑假阅读书单上
But it's on the NYU summer reading list
所以我就念了
and I'm reading it anyway, so...
我觉得也许这样能…
I thought, I don't know, maybe this way...
能帮她赶上进度
This way, she won't get behind.
想让我走的话 我可以走
I can leave, if you want.
不...不 留下 留下
No, no. Stay. Stay.
对她有好处
It'd be good for her.
科尔西医生
Dr. Kersey...
你觉得这有帮助吗
Do you think it helps?
肯定有
I know it does.
我在我的床上睡不着
I can't sleep on our bed.
于是我就睡在沙发上 看着电视 直到我昏睡
So I sleep on the couch. I watch TV until I pass out.
但就算这样
Even then I...
还是没法睡着
I'm just not getting any sleep.
这是意料之中的
That's to be expected.
如果越来越严重的话 我可以开安眠药
I can prescribe sleeping pills if it gets worse.
感觉我是在炼狱中
I feel like I'm in purgatory.
没法回去上班 没法留在家里
I can't go back to work, I can't be around my house.
我小时候
When I was a kid,
经常坐火车 来躲着我父亲
I used to ride the trains to avoid my father.
甚至在车上做作业
And I would even do my homework then,
只为了能离他远点
just to stay away from him.
所以
So...
我最近就这么做
I've been doing that.
只是坐着火车
Just riding the trains...
胡思乱想
Just to think.
我也希望我看到的一切都能让我想起露西
I wish I could say everything I see reminds me of Lucy.
但我看到的一切都让我想起他们
But everything I see reminds me of them.
我从未见过的男人
The men I've never seen.
来我家里杀了她的人
The men who came and took her from me.
我是芝加哥警察局的
This is Detective Kevin Raines
凯文·雷恩斯侦探
of the Chicago Police Department.
如果有紧急情况 请拔打报警电话
If this is an emergency, please dial 911.
否则请留言
Otherwise, please leave a message.
那是个梦
"It was a dream,
他随时都可能醒来
and that he might wake up at any moment..."
我感谢上帝给了我乔丹
I thank God for Jordan.
他们继续 一小时又一小时…
"And as they went on, hour after hour..."
我尽力保持体力
I try to stay strong.
漂亮的擦棒球
Good clean cut right there.
一周内发生了多达90起枪击案
With as many as 90 shootings in a week,
芝加哥的暴力犯罪
violent crime in Chicago
创了20年来的新高 而警方…
is now at a 20-year high, while the police...
很难摆脱我的挫折感
It's hard to escape the feeling that I failed.
没能保护我老婆
Failed to protect my wife.
没能保护我女儿
Failed to protect my daughter.
没能尽到一个男人最该尽到的责任
Failed at the most important things a man does.
- 给 孩子 - 谢谢了
- Here you go, kid. - Thanks, man.
不 不是个U
No. It's not a "U."
是个E
"E."
K-E-R-S-E-Y…
K-E-R-S-E-Y.
对 科尔西
Right. Kersey.
雷恩斯侦探不在
Detective Raines isn't in.
你想留言吗
Would you like to leave a message?
是的
Yes.
这是个过程
This is a process.
需要时间
And it's gonna take time.
我知道这是个过程
Yeah, I know it's a process.
我只是
I'm just...
很想知道个结果
Starting to wonder about the result, that's all.
我知道这过程
Listen, I understand the process
需要一些时间
takes a little bit of time, all right?
填写这申请表上的所有空格
Just fill out all the boxes on this application.
坐下等等 我们会尽快答复你
Take a seat, and we'll get to you as soon as possible.
你好 先生 填写这申请表
Hello, sir. Fill out this application,
所有空格都填写
every single box, please.
不含麸质（面筋棒）
Gluten Free Bar
先生 我能帮你什么吗
Sir, can I help you?
是的 我来找雷恩斯侦探
Yeah, I'm here to see Detective Raines.
雷恩斯侦探 你有预约吗
Detective Raines. Do you have an appointment, sir?
不 我没有
No. No, I don't.
我叫保罗·科尔西
My name is Paul Kersey.
K-U-R…
K-U-R...
E-R…
E-R...
- 对不起 - 没关系
- Sorry about that. - It's all right.
喂 科尔西医生 进来吧
Hey, Dr. Kersey. Dr. Kersey, come on back.
谢谢你 谢谢
Thank you. Thanks.
让他进来吧 威利
Buzz him in, Willy.
好
Yeah.
那个受伤歹徒的血液和皮肤
What about the DNA in the blood and skin
DNA检测结果呢
from the guy that got burned?
测试结果出来了
We got that test back.
在我们的数据库中没有匹配的人
It didn't match anybody in our database.
但如果抓到了人
But we can use it to put 'em there
就能当做证据
when we get one in custody.
我是雷恩斯
Yeah, Raines.
记下号码 我等会打给他
Get a number, I'll call him back.
CCA是什么
CCA?
已结案 凶手已逮捕
Cleared. Closed by arrest.
那么其它这些都是未破的案子？
So all these other ones are open cases?
是的
Yep.
多数都是黑帮犯罪
Most of these are gang-related.
黑帮之间的仇杀
Just asshole-on-asshole violence.
一个人在社交媒体上说了不该说的话
Some banger posts some shit on social media
就有人拿着一把AR-15去报复他
and they retaliate with an AR-15.
上周末一个人在一个派对上大开杀戒
Last weekend, a guy shot up a party.
一个人射中了14个人 却没一个目击者
One guy shoots 14 people, no one sees anything.
他们不会向警方提供线索 所以依然是未破的案子
They don't talk to the cops, that's why these stay open.
我的意思是 你老婆的案子不一样
Point is, your wife's case is different.
你想坐下吗
You wanna have a seat?
谢谢
Thanks.
三个劫匪慌了
I mean, that's three burglars who panicked.
我保证至少有一个人
I guarantee at least one of 'em
现在正担心的要命
is shittin' himself somewhere.
他一旦有个朋友
He's got a friend who's gonna get picked up
因为别的案子被捕
on something unrelated.
就会为了自己的自由出卖他的同伙
He's gonna sell his buddy down the river for his own freedom.
知道吗
Okay?
我还见过出卖自己亲娘的呢
I've seen guys turn in their own mother.
我悬赏征求线索好不好
What if I offered some kind of reward?
那样会冒出大量的假线索
We'll just get flooded with false leads.
我和搭档会把时间
Me and my partner are gonna have to
浪费在追踪假线索上
waste time tracking 'em down.
请个私家侦探如何
What about a private investigator?
如果是配偶外遇 人员失踪找私家侦探还可以
PI's good for cheating spouses, missing persons...
但侦办杀人案 只会拿钱不办事
But murder case, they'll just take your money.
他们不能参与警方调查的案子
They can't get involved in a police investigation.
否则就是破坏证据 容易被吊销执照
It's tampering with evidence, they could lose their license.
那么我就只能干等着
So there's nothing that I can do.
你是这个意思吗
Is that what you're saying?
你可以抱有信心
You can have faith.
信心对这些人有用吗
How'd faith work out for them?
This is Lake transfer to Orange...
Green, Purple, and Brown.
This is Red Line train to Howard.
我的天
Oh, shit!
你好 美女
Damn, what's up, baby?
嗨 美女
Hey, mama.
别走啊
What's poppin', redbone?
看你 你要去哪里
Look at you. Where you going, baby?
我能跟你一起去吗
Can I come with you?
看你的翘臀 看这丰满的大腿
Look at your fine ass. Look at them thick-ass thighs.
能告诉我你的号码吗 我能打给你吗
Can I get your number, baby? Can I call?
喂
Hey!
你小子说什么
What the fuck you say, puto?
别去烦她
Just leave her alone.
你在跟谁说话
Fuck you talking to?
别去烦她
Just leave her alone.
你脑子有病吗
What the fuck is your problem?
白痴
Punk-ass.
你以为你是谁啊
Who the fuck you think you are?
我开枪不是为了杀人 是为了活着
I don't shoot to kill, I shoot to stay alive.
遵纪守法的坏人是不存在的
Law-abiding criminals don't exist.
生死在一线之间时 警察却在千里之外
When seconds count, cops are minutes away.
来海盗旗体育用品店看看
Come on down to Jolly Roger's.
我们的一级枪械非常的优惠
We've got some badass deals on our F-1 firearms.
对了 现在
Ooh, and right now,
我们还有一种特别武器桌
we have a special on our tactical furniture.
让坏人措手不及
Surprise 'em.
这个适合你 小心…
Okay, here's a good one for you. Easy on the...
不 等等 年轻人
No, no, hold it, son.
第一次买枪？
First gun?
是的
Uh, yeah.
第一次压力会很大
It can be pretty overwhelming at first.
是啊
I'll say.
放心 有我帮你 我叫费雪妮
Don't worry, I got your back. I'm Bethany.
- 你好 - 欢迎光临海盗旗体育用品店
- Hi. - Welcome to Jolly Roger's.
到里面来 我给你介绍一下
Come on back, let me show you around.
这里是我们所有的刀类武器
So over here we have all of our bladed weapons.
我后面的墙上是我们所有的步枪
Behind me on this wall are all of our rifles.
每把枪都赠送一盒子弹和两个弹匣
Each one comes with a free case and two PMAGs.
请跟我来这里
And if you follow me over here,
那里是我们所有的新型手枪
all of our new pistols are over there.
我们所有的武器都在这里
And all of our used weapons are right here.
二手？
- Used? - Oh.
当然不是曾用于犯罪的枪 二手的
Not used in crimes, obviously. But, you know, used.
不知道先介绍哪一款
I don't know where to begin.
我个人最喜欢的
Well, personally, my very favorite
是这种枪
is right over here.
对不起 请问一下
Forgive me for asking,
买枪需要什么手续
but what is the process for all of this?
肯定手续很繁琐吧
There must be a lot of paperwork, right?
哦
Oh.
大可放心
Don't even worry.
我们今天就为你提供
We'll get you set up with
武器配有许可证申请表
your FOID application right here today.
州警方审查的很快
State Police send it pretty quick.
然后你要上个枪支安全课程
And then you'll just have to take a gun safety class,
但你放心 没人不及格过
but don't worry, no one ever fails.
你可以安排在
You can do that anytime within 30 days
市政府审核的30天内的任何时间
of the time period you're waiting for your city permit.
然后再过72小时
And then it's just 72 hours,
你就能全副武装 准备出击了
and you're cocked, locked, and ready to rock.
对了 我们还可以给你办强制保险
Ooh, and we can set you up with a gun safe.
如果有人偷了这把枪
If someone ever steals that gun,
通过子弹就能查出是你的枪
those bullets can be traced right back to you.
我回去考虑考虑
I'm gonna think about it...
然后再来找你
And I'll come back.
好的 来找费雪妮就可以
Great, just ask for Bethany.
科尔西医生 二号手术室 科尔西医生 二号手术室
Dr. Kersey, OR Two. Dr. Kersey, OR Two.
心跳监控器 输氧
Put him on the monitor and oxygen.
听我倒数
On my count.
3  2  1
Three, two, one.
呼吸 好的
And breathe. Good.
血袋马上送来 准备静脉注射 脱下他的裤子
Blood's on its way. Get an IV. Get his pants off.
好 放松 你没事的
Okay. Take it easy, you're okay.
你不会有事的 先生
You'll be all right, sir.
这是克拉克17手枪
This is the Glock 17,
可以说是史上最具代表性的手枪
arguably the most iconic pistol of all time.
今天 我要教你们如何拆卸它
Today, I'm gonna teach you how to take it apart.
然后用相反的步骤把枪组装起来
Then put it back together by simply reversing the steps.
向后轻推枪栓
Put slight backwards pressure on the slide,
枪栓会向前脱落
and the slide will release forward.
第三步 取下枪管
Step three, remove the barrel.
第四步
Step three...
以枪管的开口端开始刷
Brush from the breach end of the barrel.
来回四五次
I do this four to five times or until...
科尔西医生 去急诊室
Dr. Kersey to ICU.
科尔西医生请去急诊室
Dr. Kersey, please report to ICU.
她发作了一次
She's had a seizure.
她不会有事吧
Is she gonna be okay?
我们唯一确定的是
The only thing we know for sure
她苏醒的可能一天比一天小
is her odds get less every day.
她戴着束缚
She's in handcuffs.
我的女儿戴着束缚
My daughter is in handcuffs.
而伤害她的人却逍遥法外
And the men who did it are out there.
自由自在
Free.
看这些禽兽对我女儿的伤害
Look what these animals did to my baby.
- 是啊 - 是啊
- Yeah. - Yeah.
那么…
So...
钥匙 交出来
Keys, now!
喂喂 等等 拜托
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on, man. Come on, man.
给我 贱人
Give it up, bitch.
没事的 拜托
It's all right. Come on, man.
喂
Hey!
啊
Ah!
没事的 没事的 离开这里 走吧
It's okay, it's okay, get out of here. Go! Go!
让一下
Move over.
多雨的7月…
A rainy July...
机票大减价…
Tickets are now on sale for the...
芝加哥教师联合会
Chicago's teacher's union
采取了第一步…
has taken the first step...
喂
Hey!
我不认识他
I didn't know him.
他不知从哪里冒出来的
He just came out of nowhere.
他救了我的命
He saved my life.
就像一个守护天使
Like a guardian angel.
我听到了那女人喊叫
I heard that girl screaming
然后听到轮胎的摩擦声
and then I heard tires squealing,
很多次枪击 然后是撞车
a whole bunch of shots and then a crash.
那枪手呢
What about the shooter?
好像是个白人
He looked like a white dude.
穿着连帽上衣
He had a hoodie.
跟外面那对夫妻的描述相同
It's the same description the couple gave outside.
穿着连帽上衣的白人
White guy in a hoodie.
他们说他是守护天使
They called him a guardian angel.
应该说是死神才对
Yeah, more like a Grim Reaper.
你们看到他
I mean, did you see how
站在那人面前杀了他的样子吗
he stood over that guy and shot him?
很冷酷的
That shit was cold.
你看到他的面容了吗
Did you see his face?
Mmm-mmm.
他手臂上的痕迹或者纹身呢
How about marks on his arms or tattoos?
Mmm-mmm.
那么没什么对我们有用的线索？
So nothing that can help us?
当时天黑 他在开枪
It was dark. He was shooting.
呃
Um...
他一直这么甩着他的手
He kept waving his hand around like this.
好像他的手中枪了那样？
Like his hand got shot?
我哪知道 看看影片吧
I don't know. Watch the video.
你们看到的不比我少
I mean, you've seen as much as I did.
就是这里
- There! - Yeah.
不像是中枪的样子
It doesn't look like it was shot.
嗯
Hmm.
这是枪栓后坐力
No, that is the slide kicking back
划伤了他的手
and cutting his hand
因为他不知道怎么拿枪
because he doesn't know how to hold a gun.
那么嫌疑人是个以前没开枪的人？
So we're looking for a guy who never fired a gun?
没在愤怒时开枪
Well, not in anger.
他现在会了
Well, he has now.
娜塔莎 我们需要你
Natasha, listen, we're gonna need you to
把这段影片保密
keep this video confidential, okay?
不要发在社交媒体上
No posting on social media,
就像你们很多人那样
and all that stuff you guys do.
我几小时以前就发出去了
I uploaded that shit hours ago.
点阅率直接爆表
I'm getting hits like a motherfucker.
好极了
Terrific.
谁想吃面筋
Who wants gluten?
你太残忍了
Oh, man, that's just cruel.
支持一下嘛
A little support.
你知道你想吃熊爪饼
You know you want a bear claw.
是的 我想吃
Hell, yeah, I do.
甜甜圈
Donut hole.
现在是好时节 但对格兰特公园的草坪来说不是这样
It was a good time, but not for the grass in Grant Park
成千上万的参加节日的人
after hundreds of thousands of festival goers
去那里参加洛拉帕罗佐音乐节
romped through the area for Lollapalooza.
据我猜测 格兰特公园的草坪遭受了
It is estimated that there was $300,000 worth of damage
价值30万美元的损失
done to the lawn in Grant Park.
跟往常一样音乐会的主办方
As usual, the concert promoters
要为此买单
are on the hook for paying that bill.
以前的年头更严重 当多雨的季节…
It's been worse in years past, when muddy weather...
哇
Whoa!
今天的曼考节目
The water cooler talk today
主要话题是
on the Mancow Show
很多人都在看的这段影片
is everybody is watching this video,
这段疯传的穿连帽上衣人的影片
this viral video of this guy in a hoodie.
他们把他称作死神
They're calling him the Grim Reaper
杀了这些坏人 这些劫车人
that shot these bad guys, these carjackers,
目击者是这么说的 是对还是错 我不知道
according to witnesses. Right or wrong, I don't know.
是善还是恶 我不知道 我一直来回思考
Good or bad, I don't know. I go back and forth on it.
他是英雄还是坏人 这是辩论的主题
Is he a hero or a zero? That's the debate.
我们正接到听众来电
We got calls coming in.
数量就像圣诞树上的彩灯
The phones are lit up like a Christmas tree.
我认为这个人…
I say the guy's,
有的人不爱听我这话
and some people are mad at me...
我认为这个人是英雄 他制止了劫车
I say the guy's a hero. He stopped the carjacking.
他确实是英雄
He is a hero.
他是英雄还是坏人
Is he a hero or is he a zero?
你们怎么看
What do you think, Chicago?
现在给我们打电话 我是曼考
Call us right now. It's the Mancow.
我们想听到你的观点
And we wanna hear from you.
他看到有人正被抢劫
He saw somebody about to get jacked,
还是一对黑人夫妻
and a black couple at that?
权力归于死神
Power to the Grim Reaper.
我不这么认为
Yeah, but I don't know about that.
不这么认为
I don't know.
也许我们该把这个问题交给听众
And maybe that's the question we put out to the listeners.
好
Okay.
他动用私刑是正确的？
Is he right for taking the law into his own hands,
还是错误的呢 给我们打电话
or is it wrong? Give us a call.
"摇摆早晨" Shade 45频道
Sway in the Morning. Shade 45.
是的 我今天看到他了
Yeah, I saw that guy earlier today,
不过你该再去看看他
but you should check on him.
我会的
I'll check that.
这个可怜的孩子 今天上学的路上中了枪
This poor kid. Got shot on the way to school.
泰勒
Tyler.
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
嗨 泰勒 我是科尔西医生
Hi, Tyler. I'm Dr. Kersey.
我来看看你的伤 可以吗
I'm here to look at your wound. Is that all right?
我有一个发光笔
I have my little flashlight pen.
我来看一下
Let's take a look.
肯定很痛吧
That must've hurt.
你是勒布朗的球迷？
A LeBron fan?
而我
Me?
一直是乔丹的球迷
I'll always be a Jordan guy.
他有魅力 有风格 能空中飞人
He had swagger, he had style, he could fly through the air.
但勒布朗也可能是史上最棒的
Still, LeBron might be the best ever.
- 有可能 - 是啊
- Maybe. - Yeah.
你是被误伤？
You got caught in some crossfire?
是冰淇淋男干的
The Ice Cream Man done it.
冰淇淋男？
The Ice Cream Man?
不认他当老大 就无法走路去上学
Can't walk to school if you don't work for him.
是个卖冰淇淋的？
Selling ice cream?
不是
Nah.
他说下次就是我的大腿中枪
He said next time, it ain't gonna be my leg.
泰勒 你不会有事的
Tyler, you are gonna be all right.
我保证
I promise.
谢谢
Thanks.
我们等会见 好吗
I'll see you in a little while. All right?
好
Okay.
- 那个叫塔尼莎的女人 - 怎么了
- The cat, Tanisha. - Word?
好了
Yo, that's it, MUBU.
那女人才是正点 塔尼莎
That's what I'm talkin' about. Yeah, Tanisha.
她的生意高级
That was next level business she was doing.
- 在你的地盘拉皮条？ - 好的
- Pimp out your crib? - That's it.
这样好 谢谢
That's what I'm talking about. Thank you.
带她来我的地盘
Yeah, so, brought her up to my crib,
让他看看照片
show him the picture...
我当然也有
Of course I got mine,
让他看看照片 你会了解的
but show him the picture, you'll see.
- 让我看看那女人 - 喂 看这人
- Let's see that cat, man. - Hey, look here.
你就是冰淇淋男？
You're the Ice Cream Man?
你他妈是谁
Who the fuck are you?
是你最后一个顾客
Your last customer.
天啊
Oh, shit!
- 喂 给我 - 让开
- Yo, give me that shit! - Out my way.
他是个白人
He was, uh... He was white.
白人 穿着连帽上衣
A white guy, he had a hoodie...
我只知道这些
And that's all I know.
- 他身高多少 - 谢谢
- Was he tall? Short? - Thanks.
- 体型如何 -他个子不矮
- He was not short. - Fat? Skinny?
他比我高
He was taller than me, you know.
他就这么走这去…
I don't know. He just went over there...
反正就是个白人
He was just some white guy.
我来猜猜 穿着连帽上衣的白人？
Let me guess, white guy with a hoodie?
没错 穿着连帽上衣的白人
Yeah, exactly. White guy with a hoodie.
真扯 9个目击者说的都一样
Fucking bullshit. Nine witnesses, one story.
是死神
The Grim Reaper.
他们说他什么都没抢
They say he didn't take anything.
只是走这去 杀了死者就走了
Just walked up, shot the victim and left.
他叫雷·肖恩·科尔
That's Ray Shawn Core.
多起毒品贩卖和枪击案嫌疑人
Multiple drug offenses suspect and three shootings.
是个地头蛇
- Mmm, real community leader. - Yeah.
你真觉得是同一个人干的？
You really think it's the same shooter?
砰 砰 砰
Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow!
找出那段影片
Pull up that video.
- 死神的？  - 是的
- Reaper? - Yeah.
- 他用的是哪只手？ - 等等
- What hand does he shoot with? - Hold up.
砰 砰 砰
Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow!
芝加哥是不是出了个侠客
Could there be a vigilante in Chicago?
在第二次出手杀了一个地头蛇之后
Rumors are circulating after the second shooting
连日来 各种流言满天飞
of a known criminal in as many days.
警方在寻找这个人
Police are looking for this man,
芝加哥死神
the Chicago Grim Reaper.
根据描述是个30多岁的白人
Described as a white male in his mid to late 30s.
这完全是以漫画书上看到的
This is straight out of a comic book.
这个人变得如此大胆
This dude has gotten so bold.
死神干掉冰淇淋男
Grim Reaper has taken out the Ice Cream Man.
我也想穿上连帽上衣
I might as well get a hoodie and just
开始挺身而出 打击犯罪
start doin' somethin' and fighting crime...
死神不是问题所在
The Grim Reaper isn't part of the problem.
那个冰淇淋男 那个毒贩
The Ice Cream Man, the drug dealer,
才是问题所在
is part of the problem.
你要站在冰淇淋男一边？
You're gonna side with The Ice Cream Man?
有个穿连帽上衣的白人
You got a white guy in a hoodie
在杀黑人
killing black people.
你们对此没意见？
You don't have a problem with that?
他是个毒贩
- This is a drug dealer. - Hmm.
他一直欺压那些
I mean, he's making it hard for the people
住在那一地区的人
that live on that very block.
谁道我们不需要死神这样的人
Don't we need people like this Grim Reaper
来阻止恶人们吗
to keep the monsters at bay?
这是适得其反
It's a slippery slope.
现在很多人
So now everyone's just gonna
都会去私自执法了
take the law into their own hands,
去杀那些他们认为做坏事的人
kill somebody that they think is doing something wrong.
如果你有任何线索
If you have any information,
就拨打这个号码
you're asked to call this number
通知芝加哥警方
and contact the Chicago Police.
我接到很多来自休斯顿、底特律
I'm getting calls from Houston,
和纽约的电话
Detroit, New York.
都担心会引发别人的模仿 进展如何了
Everybody's nervous about a copycat. Where are we?
我们我猜测劫车那次只是偶然的
Well, we assume the carjacking was random.
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
我们的嫌犯
And our subject was just in
只是碰巧遇上了
the wrong place at the wrong time.
但这次让他尝到甜头
- But he got a taste for it. - Mmm-hmm.
所以我们在尽力分析
So we were trying to figure out
他是如何选择的第二个受害人
how he selected the second victim.
那个毒贩
- The drug dealer. - Mmm-hmm.
我们也知道他是左撇子
Oh, we also know he's left-handed.
相信他没有案底
Um, and we're pretty sure he's not in the system.
在第一次枪击后我们就判断了这一点
We figured that out after the first shooting.
他缺少基本的武器使用技能
Um, he had a lack of basic weapon skills.
至少可以这么说
To say the least.
哇 很好
Wow. Great.
你们把嫌疑人的范围缩小到100万人了
You got it narrowed down to about a million suspects.
侦探们 别再坐着了
Detectives, get off your fucking asses!
他火了
He's pissed.
你能不能告诉我
You wanna tell me
我们要去哪里
where we're gonna start looking
开始我们的大海捞针
for our white needle in the haystack?
不是哪里
Not where.
是什么时候
But when.
为什么是现在呢
I mean, why now?
是什么
What, uh...
惹毛了死神先生的导火线
Lit the fuse that set off our Mr. Reaper?
你的脸色好多了
You look much better.
谢谢 我的感觉好多了
Thank you. I feel much better.
一直在锻炼？
You exercising?
练俯卧撑
I do my push-ups.
很好 常出去与人交际吗
Mmm-hmm. Good. Getting out? Socializing?
呃
Mmm...
不太多
Not so much.
就像你说的 这是个过程
It's like you said. It's a process.
需要时间
Takes time.
不管你用了什么办法 继续保持
Well, whatever you're doing, keep it up.
好 我会的
Okay. I will.
- 继续输送 - 好的
Keep on bagging. Push the O-neg.
注射O型血
Got it!
给我超音波机器
Give me the ultrasound machine.
保持按压 给我除颤器
Hold compressions. Give me the defib.
加到300伏
Charge to 300.
天 我认识这小子
Jesus. I know this kid.
- 加压完毕 - 准备
- Charged. - Clear.
-继续输液 -再次加压到300伏
- Continue bagging. - Charge again to 300.
加压完毕
Charged.
准备
Clear.
死亡时间 晚上9点35分
Time of death, 9:35 p.m.
科尔西医生
Dr. Kersey?
周三8点 拉万达饭店
Wednesday, 8:00, La Fonda.
再见
See you guys.
你好 我是芝加哥警察局的
Hi. This is Detective Kevin Raines
凯文·雷恩斯侦探
of the Chicago Police Department.
如果有紧急情况 请拔打报警电话
If this is an emergency, please dial 911.
什么事
What?
你吓了我一跳
You scared the shit out of me.
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
你什么意思 我不能来看看我侄女吗
What do you mean? I can't check on my niece?
还有她的老爸不回我的讯息
And her dad who doesn't return my texts?
对 对不起 只是这周大忙
Yeah, yeah. Look, I'm sorry, it's been a crazy week.
是吗
Yeah?
刚回来上班 还不太适应
Still getting used to being back.
你睡眠好一些了吗
You sleeping better?
反正在我看来 你气色依然很差
'Cause I gotta tell you, you still look like shit.
谢谢你的诊断 法兰克·科尔西医生
Thanks for your diagnosis, Dr. Frank Kersey.
你去死吧 真是的
Go fuck yourself. Jesus.
走吧 我们去吃饭 我请客
Come on, let's go get a bite. I'm buyin'.
- 现在吗 - 我回去上班了
- What, now? - Hey, I'm back to work.
还是工会工资 走吧
Union wages, no less. Come on.
不 我不能去
Ah, no, no, I can't.
我还要跟一群医院同事开会
I got a meeting with a bunch of hospital staff.
好的 这个周末如何
All right. What about this weekend?
- 我们一起吃顿饭 好吗 - 好 周末更合适
- We go get a bite. Yeah? - Yeah. Yeah, that's better.
更合适 我回头会通知你 好吗
That's better. I'll call you later, all right?
你的手怎么了
What's up with your hand here?
没什么 只是一点皮肉伤 别管了
It's nothing, it's a scratch. Leave it alone.
你是不是有困谁
Look, do you need somethin'?
需要钱？要让我帮你？
Some cash? What, some help?
是为了这事吗
Is that what this is about?
- 不是 - 法兰克
- No. - Frank.
给 没什么
Here, it's all right.
这是我欠你的两千块钱 给
Look, this is the $2,000 I owed you. Here you go.
没什么
It's all right.
我本想带你去吃个饭
I wanted to maybe take you to lunch, you know.
庆祝一下我有能力还你钱了
Celebrate that I can actually pay you back.
没什么
It's all right.
- 法兰克 - 再见
- Frank. - Later, man.
- 我们回头见 - 好
- I'll see you. - Yeah.
喂 朋友 你不能来这里
Hey, hey, buddy, you can't be back here.
我来找崔波
I'm looking for Trebol.
就是我 现在你可以出去了
Well, you found him, now you can get out.
米格尔要我来的
Miguel sent me.
哪个米格尔？
Who the fuck is Miguel?
他是我的饭店的一个少爷
He works as a valet at my restaurant.
手腕上纹着MJ
He's got an MJ tattooed on his wrist.
他说能在你这里为我老婆买个礼物
He said you could help me find a gift for my wife.
他是你的员工？
He works for you?
是的
Yes.
在你的饭店？
At your restaurant?
是的
Yes.
好的 请坐
Yeah, all right. Sit down.
喂
Hey.
“芝加哥北医院”
那么
So, uh...
你买礼物 是为了感谢
Is this a "thanks for the years of service"
你老婆多年的付出
kind of thing, honey,
还是为了
or is this more of
跟保姆有私情表示歉意
a "sorry, I boned the babysitter" kind of thing?
都不是
Neither.
那件事的医生刚进来了 快过来
The doctor from that thing just walked in get over there
那么你要买一件
So you're looking for something...
具体的礼物？
Specific?
很具体
Very specific.
有多么具体
Well, how specific are we talking?
沛纳海手表 你这里有卖的吗
Panerai watches. You got any of those?
我来看看
Well, why don't you just let me check
这里的收藏品
the reserve collection over here,
我觉得这里可能有东西
because I think there's something here
是你感兴趣的
that might interest you.
放下
Drop it.
- 放下了 - 踢到一边
- Fuck! It's dropped. - Kick it away.
我想要我的东西
I want my stuff.
在后面
It's in the back.
一直走
Keep moving.
小鱼是谁
Who's Fish?
他只是个送货的
He's just a drop guy.
你的人抢了我房子的东西
Yeah. Your crew that stole the shit out of my house!
我店里的东西基本都是偷来的
You just described half the shit in my shop, man.
你们还杀了我老婆
And you killed my wife!
听着
Look.
- 我只认识小鱼 - 他们是谁
- Who are they? - I just know Fish, okay?
另外的人我不认识
I don't know the other guys. I told you!
- 都在这里 都在这里 - 闭嘴
- Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. - It's all here. It's all here.
我不是根据房子放置的
I don't organize it by house,
把你房子里的东西都拿走吧
just take whatever's yours, all right?
你要说话？
What, are you gonna talk?
还是告诉我的东西在哪里
Or are you gonna tell me where my shit is?
在这里
It's here.
在哪里 不告诉我的话
Where is it? I'm gonna blow your fucking head off
就打爆你的头
if you don't tell me...
这是什么 这是什么破玩意
What the... What is this? What is this bullshit?
接下来三秒
Now you're gonna tell me where it is
你告诉我在哪里 否则就崩掉你的脑袋
in the next three seconds or your head comes off.
好了 都在这里
All right. It's all there.
你看到这个了吗 你知道这是什么吧
You see this? You know what it is, don't ya?
这本来是戴在我老婆手腕上的
It was on my wife's arm.
但愿你觉得值得
I hope it was worth it, asshole.
如果早知道
If I knew...
如果早知道是你的东西 我不会拿的
If I knew it was your shit, I wouldn't have taken it, man.
要不是我对老婆和家人的爱
All my love for my wife and my family is keeping me
我早就在你嘴里来一枪了
from putting one right in your fucking mouth.
我不是杀手 我从不杀人
I'm not a killer, okay? I don't kill people.
我不是那种人
It's not what I do.
该死的
Fuck!
混蛋
Motherfucker!
该死的
Shit!
操
Fuck!
Oh, shit!
操
Fuck!
Shit!
我没杀她
I didn't shoot her. I didn't shoot her.
我发誓 我没杀她
I promise, I didn't shoot her.
操
Fuck!
- 是谁杀的 - 不是我
- Who did? - It wasn't me.
操 拜托你
Fuck! Please!
- 不是我 是乔 - 什么
- It wasn't me. It's Joe. - What?
- 乔 - 乔什么
- Joe! - Joe who?
乔·甘农
Joe Gannon!
汽车修理店的那个油腻的家伙
The fat greasy fuck at the auto body shop.
- 乔在哪里 - 我的手机上有
- Where's Joe? - It's in my phone.
有照片 啥都有 我会带你去找他
It's got pictures, everything. I'll bring you to him.
蠢货
Stupid motherfuck.
看着我在接下来所做的事
Watch what I do in the next few seconds.
你可能会学到
You might learn something
帮你解决麻烦的办法
that could help you solve your problem.
拿起这把电钻
Grab this drill.
我要在这周围
I'm going to drill several holes
钻几个孔
around this circle right here.
这样一来
And when I do that,
这金属盒里的所有资料
the information that's inside of this metal box
就会很难再被读取了
will be a lot harder to access.
运气好的话 你的金属盒子
With any luck, your metal box
会变成这个样子
should now look something like this.
联邦调查局 中情局 国安局 国际刑警组
Again, FBI, CIA, NSA, Interpol,
我制作这段影片提供娱乐
this video was strictly made for entertainment purposes.
别去闯祸 你们这些疯狂的年轻人
Stay out of trouble, you crazy kids.
早 保罗
Morning, Paul!
死神来了
Reaper alert!
死神来了 死神来了
Reaper alert! Reaper alert!
那死神在哪里
Where's the Reaper?
死神再次出手
The Grim Reaper strikes again.
这次是在皮尔森地区
This time in the Pilsen neighborhood.
我正在这家白酒商店前
In front of this liquor store,
这里也是一处赃物交易的黑市
which was a fencing operation for stolen goods.
但现在不是了 昨天晚上
Not anymore, when last night,
死神来拜访了他们
the Grim Reaper paid them a visit.
我看这去 看到了
Dude, I look over, I see
一个白人老头走了出来
this dude walking out, this old white dude,
戴着风帽走出来
and he's walking with his hood up,
样子很可疑
looking super suspicious.
就是这样
Just like, you know...
现在已经把他偶像化了
Kind of idolizing him. Man, right now,
网络上都是这个人的事蹟
this dude is all over the Internet, man.
- 还有表情包呢 - 不是吧
- There's memes coming up. - Get outta here.
是的 有表情包 有人做了表情包
Yeah, there's memes. Like, people are making memes.
看看这个
Look at this one right here.
这个太夸张了
Oh, that's too intense.
他成了民间英雄
He's become a folk hero.
他是这些人真正的英雄
He's a real hero to these people.
他们一直遭受所在生活区的
They're being affected by all this crime
犯罪活动的影响
in their neighborhood.
只要不是在你的生活区
As long as it's not in your neighborhood.
很显然 他的样子
Clearly, if he didn't just kill somebody,
就像是刚杀了人
I don't know what he did.
我依然坚持我的观点
I still stand by my point that
我们是在把一个危险的行为正常化
we're normalizing dangerous behavior.
我们是不是应该
You know? Should we be policing ourselves
在我们的生活区维持治安
in our own neighborhoods...
多年来我一直说我们需要死神这样的人
I have said we need a guy like Grim Reaper for years.
你是否支持死神
Are you Team Reaper or not?
请致电"摇摆早晨"
Give us a call. Sway in the Morning
Shade 45频道 天狼星卫星广播公司
at Shade 45, Sirius XM.
科尔西医生
Dr. Kersey,
我们是雷恩斯侦探和杰克森侦探
it's Detective Raines and Jackson.
我们能进去吗
May we come in?
当然可以 请进
Of course. Come on in.
你好 很抱歉这么不请自来
How you doing? Sorry to drop in like this.
不用
Oh, no.
我们发现了一些情况
Uh, something's come to our attention.
希望能听听你的看法
We were hoping you could offer some insight.
很高兴见到你们 请坐
I'm happy to see you guys. Have a seat.
- 谢谢 - 谢谢
- Thanks. - Thank you.
好
Okay, um...
你见过这个人吗
Have you ever seen this man?
没有
No.
他是嫌疑人吗
Is he a suspect?
他叫塔特·卡普 绰号小鱼
Well, his name is Tate Karp. He goes by "The Fish."
他是个职业窃贼 我们相信
He's a career burglar and, we believe,
他也参与了你老婆的枪击案
involved in your wife's shooting.
你们是怎么找到他的
How did you find him?
他是怎么说的
What did he say?
遗憾的是 他昨晚被杀
Well, unfortunately, he was killed last night
我们没有机会能审问他
before we had a chance to question him.
但我们在犯罪现场发现了这个戒指
But we did find this ring at the crime scene.
这是我的戒指
That's my ring.
是啊 我们也是这么想的
Yeah. That's what we thought.
但这个戒指
Um, but this right here,
就是我们一直在等待的突破口
it's the break we've been waiting for.
- 这太好了 - 是啊
- It's great. - Yeah.
现在我们查到了卡普 我们迟早会
Now that we have Karp, it's just a matter of time
查出他们所有人
before we have the rest of 'em.
我们会查阅他的前科 看他喜欢跟谁合作
We'll run through his priors, see who he liked to work with,
调阅他的手机纪录 他的讯息
subpoena his cell phone records, his texts.
甚至是手机的GPS定位
Even the phone's GPS.
好极了 还有别的需要我帮忙的吗
Great. Do you need anything else from me?
谢谢了 目前就这些
Appreciate that. I think we're good for now.
我知道你一直为此事焦虑 我就想
Um... I know you've been frustrated and I wanted to
亲自来告诉你这个好消息
come by in person to give you the good news.
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you very much.
我跟你说过要抱有信心
I told you to have faith.
谢谢你抽出时间
Thanks for your time.
谢谢
Thank you.
喂 已经打烊了 朋友
Yo, we're closed, pal.
你是乔吧
You're Joey, right?
是的 你是谁
Yeah. Who the fuck are you?
喂 白痴 我说了打烊了
Hey, fuckstick, I said we were closed.
怎么了 放开我
What the fuck? Get me the fuck outta here.
操 放开我
Fuck! Get me the fuck outta here, man!
- 你干什么 - 闭上嘴
- What the fuck are you... - Shut the fuck up.
你要告诉我想知道的
You're gonna tell me what I wanna hear.
你不想注射它 但你猜怎么着
You don't want this. But guess what?
会给你注射一些
You'll get some.
我来帮你注射
I'm just gonna help you out.
相信我 我知道在哪里切开
Trust me, I know where to cut.
这里…不要动
Now right back here, don't move...
是你的坐骨神经
...is your sciatic nerve.
是人体内最长、最强的神经
Longest, strongest nerve in the body.
操
Fuck!
该死的
God damn!
你就是那个医生
You're that doctor.
我就是那个医生
I am that doctor.
但现在我是你的医生
But right now, I'm your doctor.
你的朋友小鱼已经死了
Your friend, Fish, is already dead.
你可以感谢他把你供了出来
You can thank him for giving you up.
不 不 不
No. No, no, no, no.
现在我想知道 还有谁去这我家
What I want to know is who else was there.
没别人
Nobody.
还有谁去这
Who else was there?
没别人
No one, man.
你感觉到的 是腐蚀性物质
What you're feeling is a caustic agent
直接作用于神经上
being applied directly to a nerve.
在医学院 我们学到
In med school, we were taught that
这是一个人能忍受的
this is the most painful experience
最大疼痛体验
that a person can endure
又不至于引发心跳停止
without possibly going into cardiac arrest.
请住手 好痛
Please stop. It hurts.
坏消息是
The bad news is
你这里有好多瓶刹车油
you've got a shit ton of brake fluid here.
所以我们要在这里玩上一整夜
So we might be here all night.
你到底说还是不说
Now you're gonna start talking, aren't ya?
诺克斯 他叫诺克斯
Knox! That's his name. Knox!
诺克斯 他的全名是什么
Knox. What's his full name?
别的我都不知道
I don't know anything else, man!
他叫诺克斯 他来自南区
His name is Knox and he's from the South Side.
都是小鱼安排的
Look, Fish planned the whole fucking thing!
我以前以没见这那个人
I never met the guy before!
我去哪里能找到诺克斯
Where do I find Knox?
你找不到 只有他来找你
You don't. He finds you.
- 乔 - 别的我都不知道
- Joe. - I don't know anything else!
我对天发誓
I swear to fucking God!
我没理由护着那个混蛋
I have no reason to protect this asshole!
我根本不认识他 你一定要相信我 拜托你
I don't even fucking know him! You gotta believe me, please.
我发誓
I fucking swear it!
我相信你 乔
I believe you, Joe.
你能感觉到异丙酚渐渐缓解
I think you're gonna find the propofol is wearing off.
谢谢你的帮助
Thanks for your help.
操
Fuck.
那么你不会杀我？
So you're not gonna kill me?
不会
No.
杀你的是千斤项
The jack is.
漂亮的击球
Damn. Hell of a swing.
还是左撇子呢
Lefty, no less.
嗨 法兰克
Hey, Frank.
我问你的长官
You know, when I asked your supervisor
你下班后常去哪里玩
where you like to hang out after work,
他说是这里
he told me here.
我还以为他忽悠我
I thought he was jerking my chain.
后来我查了一下你
Then I looked you up.
你曾是个新秀
You were a legitimate prospect.
怎么不打球了
What happened?
你们想要我签名？
So you want my autograph?
我们只想谈谈
We just wanna talk.
好的
All right.
你听说过人们最近谈论的
Have you heard of this Grim Reaper fellow
这个死神吗
that people are talking about?
是的 我听说过
Yeah, yeah. I heard about it.
他昨晚去了一家酒品店
Well, last night, he went into a liquor store.
杀了闯入你哥家里的
And he killed one of the three men
三个人之一
that broke into your brother's house.
交通监视器拍到他进出那里 白人 健壮
Traffic cam caught him walking in and out. White, fit...
- 左撇子 - 对 他是个左撇子
- Lefty. - Lefty. Yeah. He's a lefty.
然后我就问自己：
So I ask myself, you know,
我认识哪个道上的左撇子？
"What streetwise lefty do I know?"
那种能到处放话
You know, the kind of guy that could
重金征求线索
put word out he would pay for info.
会想杀了我们的嫌疑人
Would want to execute our suspects.
那种喜欢亲力亲为的人
A real do-it-himself kind of guy.
那么你们觉得这事跟我有关
So you think I had something to do with it, huh?
你们该问问我哥
Well, you should talk to my brother.
他会告诉你我不会出钱买任何东西
He'll tell you that I don't pay for shit.
当然 能让我们看看你的手吗
Of course. So, do you mind if we see your hands?
喂
Hey!
今晚在恩格尔伍德西区发生一起悲剧
Tragedy struck earlier this evening in West Englewood,
警方认为
where police think
一位49岁的三个孩子的父亲
a 49-year-old father of three was killed
在动用私刑时被杀
while trying to commit vigilante justice.
警方认为此人是模仿
Police believe this was a copycat
所谓的"芝加哥死神"
of the so-called "Chicago Grim Reaper."
他出去试图打击犯罪
A guy who went out, tried to fight crime,
最后却成了犯罪的受害人
and ended up a victim himself.
警方依然在寻找枪手
Police are still looking for the shooter.
马上接电话 否则我就告诉警察你昨晚去了哪里
Answer now or I'll tell the cops where you were last night
我是保罗·科尔西
This is Paul Kersey.
我听说你在找我
I hear you're looking for me.
是的
That's right.
到Blowout来 在阿什兰的一家夜店
Come to Blowout. Last club off Ashland.
我在那里等你
I'll be waiting.
我为何会去呢
Why would I do that?
因为去那里安全 是公共场所
Because it's safe. Public.
而且我想告诉你你老婆的遗言是什么
And I wanna tell you what your wife's last words were.
给你30分钟时间
You have 30 minutes.
开门 保罗
Come on, Paul.
保罗 开门
Paul, come on, man.
我们得谈谈 保罗
We gotta talk, Paul.
嗨
Hey, man.
你在吗
Are you here?
嗨
Hey, man.
保罗
Paul.
我来了
I'm here
出去
Get out.
我是杰克森
Jackson.
- 怎么了 - 我们这就去
- What? - We're on our way.
市区一家夜店发生交火
Shooting at a club downtown.
穿连帽上衣的人掏出一把枪
Guy in a hoodie pulled out a gun,
后来自己也中枪 在人群中跑掉了
then got shot himself. Ran out in the crowd.
喂 通知所有当地医院
Hey. Alert all the local hospitals, all right?
有任何来治疗枪伤的
Any gunshot wound being treated,
40或50多岁的男性 就给我们打电话
a male, 40s or 50s, give us a call!
具里报告说 他们没有
County reports they have no one
符合对枪手描述的人
matching the shooter's description.
其中一个伤者正前往芝加哥北医院
One of the victims is en route to Chicago North.
他说他看到了枪手
He says he saw the shooter.
病人在这边
The patient's this way.
你好
How you doing?
你看到枪手了？
Did you see the shooter?
是的 我看到了
Yeah, I did.
你能描述一下他的样子吗
Can you describe him to us?
操
Fuck!
打开
- Open it. - Uh-huh.
保罗 你要把我也杀了？
Paul, what you gonna do? Shoot me, too?
你来这里干什么
What are you doing here?
我来这里干什么？你来这里干什么
What am I doing here? What are you doing here?
这是你的情报室？
What is this, your little war room?
别指责我
Don't you judge me!
我没指责你 我是担心你
I'm not judging you! I'm worried about you!
你不能这么做
You... You can't do this.
保罗 你不是警察
Paul, you're not a cop.
总要有人做些什么
Then somebody has to do it!
我的老婆女儿就这么没了
My wife and daughter just disappear.
却没人得到惩罚
And there's no consequences.
该做的一切我都做了
I did everything I was supposed to do.
一切
Everything.
我努力工作 遵纪守法
I worked hard. I obeyed the law.
让我的家人 让我的老婆和女儿过上了好日子
I made a life for my family. For my wife and daughter!
然后呢 就这么算了？
And what? Just forget about that?
她们就这么没了？
They're just gone now?
你现在快走 法兰克
You need to leave now, Frank.
我不想让你扯上牵连
I don't want you to be part of this.
不 喂 我已经扯上牵连了
No. Hey, hey. I'm already a part of this.
留在这里
Stay, stay.
这不是芝加哥警方吗
If it isn't Chicago's finest.
你好 法兰克
Hello, Frank.
我们以为会是你哥
We were expecting your brother.
他出门了 有个聚会 什么事
Yeah, he's out. Dinner party. Why, what's up?
他可能惹上大麻烦了
Well, he could be in real trouble.
你可能不信 我们是想帮他
Believe or not, we wanna help.
太客气了 我感谢你的关心 侦探
That's so sweet. I appreciate your concern, Detective.
就像我说的 看到他的时候我会告诉他的
Like I said, when I see him, I'll tell him.
他在鬼扯
That was some bullshit.
他肯定在家
He's in there.
但没有铁证的话
But we're not arresting the surgeon
我们不能逮捕外科医生
without an ironclad proof.
好消息是我不再是嫌疑犯了
Well, the good news is I'm not a suspect anymore.
坏消息是 我不再是嫌疑犯了
The bad news is I'm not a suspect anymore.
保罗 这事必须结束
Paul, this has to end.
必须结束
It's gotta end, man.
我可不想把你埋在你老婆旁边
I don't wanna have to bury you next to your wife.
你不会埋我
You're not gonna bury me.
我们必须想办法
All right. We gotta figure this out
如果有什么警方能查出来的
if you think there's anything the cops can find.
那家夜店里有监视器
There were cameras in the club.
我自始至终都低着头
I kept my head down the whole time.
你的车呢
Where's your car?
在医院附近
Near the hospital.
你要把车开走
Okay, you gotta get it,
趁警方还没开始检查车牌
before the police start checking tags.
好
Okay.
是谁在凌晨两点半打电话
Who'd be calling at 2:30 in the morning?
我看看
Let's see.
是医院
It's the hospital.
喂
Hello?
谢谢 我会去的
Thank you. I'll be right there.
是乔丹 她苏醒了
It's Jordan. She's awake.
孩子
Oh, baby.
爸爸
Daddy.
嗨 爸爸
Hi, Daddy.
孩子
Baby.
爸爸 他们不告诉我妈妈在哪里
Dad, they won't tell me where Mom is.
爸爸 妈妈在哪里
Dad, where is Mom?
我想见妈妈 她在哪里 告诉我 爸爸 她在哪里
I wanna see Mom. Where is she? Please, Dad, where is she?
天
Oh, Jesus.
- 嗨 - 她怎么样了
- Hey. - How's she doing?
以身体上讲 我一周后就能带她回家
Physically, I can take her home in a week.
以精神上 她刚知道母亲去世了
Mentally, she just found out her mother died.
天啊 保罗
Jesus, Pauly.
这真是个奇迹
It's a miracle though, you know,
她苏醒了 这是个奇迹
that we got her back. It's a miracle.
这是个奇迹
It was a miracle.
现在唯一重要的是
All that matters now is that...
你要照顾她
You look after her.
是的 当然
Yes, of course.
必须是你 她的父亲
You, though. Her father.
我会的
I will.
不是那摊子事 也不能找别人 只有你
Not this other thing, not this other guy. You.
那事结束了
It's over.
结束了
好
Okay.
- 慢点 - 谢谢
- Slowly. - Thanks.
你确定你能行？
You sure you got everything?
是的 我能行
Yeah, I got it.
你扶着她？
You got her, Dad?
我能行 爸爸 我没事
I got it, Dad. I'm okay.
- 好 我知道你能行- 慢着点
- All right, I know you got it. - Easy does it.
真想不到我要坐着轮椅出院
I can't believe I have to leave in this,
感觉我是个残疾人
I feel like an invalid.
你不是残疾人
You're not an invalid.
- 再见 乔丹 - 再见
- Bye, Jordan. - Bye.
- 你准备好了吗 - 是的 带我回家吧
- You ready? - Yes, take me home.
- 嗨 科尔西医生 - 科尔西医生
- Hey, Dr. Kersey. - Dr. Kersey.
- 乔丹 - 乔丹
- Jordan. - Jordan.
我跟你们说过 等她能记起来什么 我们就给你们打电话
I told you guys, we'll call you as soon as she remembers something.
没关系 爸爸 呃
It's okay, Dad. Um...
我想帮助你们 真的
I wanna help you guys, I really do.
只不过
It's just that...
我上楼拿iPad之后的事情我都记不起来了
I don't remember anything after going upstairs to get the iPad.
你能记起来的任何细节
Any little detail you can remember
都能对我们有很大的帮助 乔丹
will really help us out a lot, Jordan.
我什么都不记得 抱歉
I don't remember a thing. I'm sorry.
没关系 也许这段时间你能记起来什么
It's okay. Maybe over time, you'll remember something.
不管怎么样 我们都会一直追查他们
Either way, we'll, uh, we'll keep looking for the guys.
- 谢谢 - 谢谢你们
- Thank you. - Thanks, guys.
- 科尔西医生 - 我们会通知你们的
- Dr. Kersey. - We'll let you know.
再见
Bye.
梅瑞迪斯医生
Dr. Meredith,
梅瑞迪斯医生 请前往…
Dr. Ronald Meredith, please report...
感觉他们很好的
Well, they seem okay.
等一下
Hey, hold that.
谢谢
Thank you.
你是怎么了
What happened to you?
哦 我出了一点意外
Oh, um, I was in an accident.
对不起
Oh, I'm sorry.
好一些了吗
Are you better?
是的
Yeah.
那很好
That's nice.
你要回家？
You going home?
是的 我要回家
Yeah. I'm going home.
我也要回家
I'm going home, too.
你是怎么了
Well, what happened to you?
我中了枪
I got shot.
哦
Oh, well...
很高兴你没事了
I'm glad you're okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
保重
Take care.
回头见 科尔西医生
I'll see you around, Dr. Kersey.
爸爸 那是谁啊
Dad, who was that?
不知道 孩子 是别人的病人
Not a clue, honey. Somebody else's patient.
欢迎来到海盗旗体育用品店 我能帮你什么
Welcome to Jolly Roger's. How can I help you?
我想买把枪
I wanna buy a gun.
我是不是认识你
Don't I know you?
是的 我在学写作和历史
Yeah, I'm taking Writing and History.
主要是入门课程
Mainly just introduction classes.
我在网络上学习 每天有几个小时
I'm doing it online, just a couple hours a day.
这样秋天升学后
So that way, I don't fall behind
我就能赶上进度
when school starts next fall.
这样好
Well, that's smart.
我觉得你是我们家族最有才学的
You know, I think you're the smartest one in the family.
你的治疗怎么样了
So how's your therapy coming?
看你恢复的差不多了
'Cause you look like you're getting around better.
很好的 很无聊 我快完成了
It's good. You know, boring. I'm almost done,
但我还要让我的身体
but I just had to teach my body
试着去做基本的动作
how to do basic things again.
有你在家感觉真好
It feels good to have you home.
回家的感觉很好
Feels good to be home.
中间那个人就是他 他和他女儿
And that's him in the middle. Him and the girl.
再见 法兰克叔叔 爱你
Good night, Uncle Frank. Love you!
好的 法兰克
Okay, Frankie!
爸爸 厨房打扫干净了 我要去睡了
Dad, the kitchen's clean. I'm going to bed.
好的 孩子
Okay, honey.
喂 你能帮我一下吗
Hey, can you help me with this?
- 挪动一点点  - 挪动它？
- Move this? - Slide it down a little.
是的 就一点点
Yeah, just a little bit. Mmm-hmm.
为什么要挪动它
Why are you moving this?
因为我要你到这里来
Because I need you to come over here.
我刚看到有个人经过
I just saw somebody run by.
什么人经过？
What do you mean you just saw someone run by?
- 你看到有人经过这里？ - 是的 是的
- You saw someone run by here? - Yeah, I did. I did.
我要你到楼梯下
I want you to get under the stairs.
爸爸 你为什么让我到楼梯下
Dad, why are you putting me under the stairs?
- 马上打电话报警 - 爸爸一定要小心
- Call the cops right now. - Dad, please be careful.
- 用你的手机报警 - 爸爸 拜托
- Take your phone and dial 911. - Dad, please!
911勤务中心 你有什么麻烦？
911, what is your emergency?
有人正要闯进我家
There's men, they're breaking into my house.
他们在我家的草坪上
They're on my front lawn.
好像是来杀我的
I think they're coming to kill me.
我叫乔丹·科尔西
My name is Jordan Kersey.
我在艾文思顿的多塞特路20号
I'm at 20 Dorset Road in Evanston.
他们好像进来了
I think they're here.
乔丹 我没事
Jordan, I'm okay.
爸爸 爸爸
Dad. Dad!
安静 等着警察来
Stay quiet. Just wait for the police.
不要出来 留在里面
Do not come out. Stay in there.
坐下
Sit down.
爸爸
Dad?
他们好像刚打中了我爸
I think they just shot my dad.
爸爸 爸爸
Dad! Dad!
乔丹 留在那里
Jordan, just stay up there!
是你女儿吗
Is that your little girl?
你听说过有人被烧死吗
Now, you ever hear someone burn to death?
会让你满意的 科尔西医生
You're in for a treat, Dr. Kersey.
爸爸
Dad!
你是说你手上的
So you're saying you got both the cut
基本痊愈的伤口
on your hand that's almost healed
和肩膀上的伤口都是今晚的伤 是这样吗
and the shot in the shoulder tonight? That's your story.
这是事实 是这样的
That's what happened. That's my story.
嗯
Hmm.
手枪和步枪的许可证呢
And the paperwork for the pistols and the rifle?
你可以给海盗旗体育用品店打电话
You can call Jolly Roger's Sporting Goods.
找费雪妮问问
Ask for Bethany.
你买这些枪都是在…
And you bought these guns...
我女儿回家的那一天
The day my daughter came home.
只为了应对万一再发生这样的事
Just in case something like this ever happened again.
有把克拉克手枪吗
What about a Glock?
我之前有一把 后来决定把它扔了
I had one for a while. Decided to get rid of it.
早就没了？
Gone for good?
是的 早就没了
Yeah. Gone for good.
我没别的问题了
Well, I got everything I need.
看起来案情很简单 诺克斯回来了
Seems pretty straightforward. Knox came back,
因为他觉得乔丹有可能认出他
'cause he thought Jordan could ID him.
然后你像所有男人一样 保护了自己的家人
And you defended your family like any man would.
谢谢
Thank you.
科尔西医生 请继续拯救大家性命
And Dr. Kersey, stick to saving lives.
你擅长救人
You're good at it.
我会的
I will.
谢谢你
Thanks for everything.
你满意了吗
So, you satisfied?
不
No.
现在我满意了
Now I'm satisfied.
摇摆早晨
Sway in the Morning,
Shade 45频道 天狼星卫星广播公司
Shade 45 at Sirius XM.
现在，芝加哥有了好消息
Hey,listen.We finally have some great news come to Chicago.
今年暴力犯罪发生率首次下降
Violence crime has dropped for the first time in the year.
喂 死神
Hey, Grim Reaper,
我们不知道你在哪里 去过哪里
we don't know where you are, where you went,
经历了什么
or what happened to you,
不管你是谁 坚持住
whoever that is, stay there. Peace.
我有说过我多么以你为荣吗
Have I told you how proud I am with you?
是的 爸爸 你对我说过无数次了
Yes, Dad, you've told me, like, a billion times.
如果你需要什么 我就在三站之外
If you ever need anything, I'm just three stops away.
我知道 爸爸 我有你的号码
I know, Dad. I've got the number.
我爱你
I love you.
我爱你 孩子
I love you, honey.
你可以走了
Well, you can go now.
好 去好好学习
All right. Go be smart.
再见 孩子
Bye, baby.
喂
Hey!
原字幕为 致远淡泊 在
https://www.zimuku.cn/detail/106996.html上传的字幕